Guide to the Arthur Levitt, Jr. Papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series XIII: SEC Correspondents Index
  - Raines, Frank D. Office of Management and Budget; Fannie Mae; TO: Oct. 7, 1996; Jan. 29, 2001
  - Raschke, Don North American Securities Administrators Association, Inc. - Investment Companies Sales Practice Committee, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Rashbaum, Harold, FROM: Jun. 9, 1997; TO: Jul. 1, 1997
  - Razaghian, Rose, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Readmond, Ron Charles Schwab & Co, Inc, TO: Feb. 17, 1995
  - Regan, Andrew Harvard University - Graduate School of Business Administration, TO: May 1, 1995
  - Regan, Ned Jerome Levy Economics Institute; CUNY Baruch College; FROM: Apr. 17, 2000; Jul. 20, 2000; Jan. 24, 2001 (2); TO: Apr. 25, 2000; Aug. 31, 2000; Jan. 29, 2001
  - Rehnquist, William H. US Supreme Court, TO: Oct. 5, 1998
  - Reich, Robert (Biff) Secretary of Labor, FROM: Sep. 10, 1996 (Skip Hayward); TO: Sep. 19, 1996
  - Reilly, Richard M. Allmerica Investments, Inc. TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Reis, Donald Securities Division, NV, TO: Apr. 21, 1995
  - Reischauer, Robert Brookings Institution, TO: Oct. 21, 1998
  - Rendell, Edward G. Mayor, Philadelphia, PA, FROM: Apr. 15, 1999; TO: Dec. 29, 1998; May 5, 1999
  - Reno, Janet Attorney General, USA, FROM: Jun. 5, 1995; Aug. 25, 1997; TO: Jun. 14, 1995; Dec.[1-4], 1995; Sep. 22, 1997; Sep. 25, 1997; Jun. 9, 1999
  - Revson, Charles Charles H. Revson Foundation, FROM: Jan. 25, 1996; TO: [Mar. 5], 1996
  - Rhett, John T., III Robinson Humphrey Co., LLC. TO: May 14, 1998
  - Riccio, Willis H. National Association of Securities Dealers Regulation, Inc. TO: May 14, 1998
  - Rice, Norman B. Mayor, Seattle, VA; US Conference of Mayors (President), FROM: Apr. 24, 1996; TO: Jun. 7, 1996
  - Rich, Linda Dallas US House of Representatives, TO: Mar. 5, 1997
  - Richard, Oliver G., III Columbia Gas System, Inc. TO: Dec. 5, 1997
  - Richards, Lori A. US SEC - Office of Compliance Inspections and Examinations, TO: May 14, 1998; Feb. 26, 1999; Mar. 3, 2000
  - Richardson, Alan H. American Public Power Association, TO: Jan. 9, 1997
  - Richardson, Bill US House of Representatives, FROM: Sep. 5, 1995; Oct. 8, 1996; TO: Nov. 4, 1996; Feb. 18, 1997
  - Richardson, Christine US SEC - Division of Market Regulation, TO: Nov. 16, 1998; Dec. 11, 2000
  - Richardson, Margaret Milner US Department of Treasury - IRS, FROM: Jun. 3, 1996; TO: Jun. 26, 1996
  - Rickson, Kenneth M. MML Investors Services, Inc. TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Ready, Marjorie, TO: Nov. 29, 2000
  - Reddy, Michael Global Financial Market Group, TO: Aug. 16, 1999
  - Reed, John S. Citicorp, FROM: Oct. 17, 1995; TO: Nov. 15, 1995; Apr. 17, 1998; Dec. 28, 1998; Jan. 5, 1999
  - Rees, Rachel L. TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Ridings, Dorothy S. Council on Foundations, FROM: Apr. 30, 1997; TO: Jun. 5, 1997
  - Ridings, C. Leslie Heather Investments, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Riegle, Donald W. US Senate, TO: Jan. 21, 1994
  - Rifkind, Robert S. Charles H. Revson Foundation, TO: Jun. 4, 1998
  - Rittmaster, D. Paul, FROM: Jul. 28, 1999; TO: Sep. 1, 1999
  - Rivera-Dirks, Catherine, FROM: Jun. 26, 1995 (filed under Odeen, Jul. 17, 1995)
  - Rivera-Dirks, John Willams College, FROM: Feb. 5, 1997 (Filed under Henning, Madge, Feb. 6, 1997); Jun. 4, 1998 (addressed to Walter, RE: Dirks)
  - Rivers, Lynn N. US House of Representatives, FROM: Oct. 10, 1996; TO: Dec. 10, 1996
  - Rivkin, Robert, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Rivlin, Alice Federal Reserve Board, TO: Dec. 23, 1998
  - Roach, Rae, TO: Feb. 23, 1995
  - Robb, Charles S. US Senate, FROM: Feb. 2, 2000; TO: Mar. 14, 2000
  - Robbins, Rachel J.P. Morgan & Co., Inc. TO: Mar. 16, 1999
  - Robbins, Ronald Liberty Securities Corporation, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Robert, Stephen Oppenheimer & Co., Inc, TO: Mar 2, 1995; TO: Apr. 20, 1995; Jun. 7, 1995
  - Roberts, Bert C. MCI Communications Corporation, FROM: May 15, 1997; TO: Jun. 5, 1997
  - Roberts, Peter A. College Savings Bank, FROM: Jan. 11, 1995; TO: Feb. 17, 1995
  - Robinson, George S., III Robinson & Langenberg, PC. FROM: Apr. 19, 2000
  - Robinson, Gerald W. II W.S. Griffith & Co., Inc. TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Robinson, Todd A. Linsco/Private Ledger Corp. TO: Feb. 17, 1995; Mar. 2, 1995; TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Roby, Joe L. Donaldson, Lufkin & Jenrette, TO: Nov. 23, 1998
  - Roche, Gerard R. Heidrick & Struggles, FROM: Aug. 3, 1998; TO: Aug. 17, 1998; Jan. 29, 2001
  - Rock, Arthur Intel Corporation; Arthur Rock & Co. FROM: Sep. 4, 1996; Sep. 23, 1998; TO: Dec. 12, 1996; Oct. 14 1998
  - Rock, Kent City Treasurer, Boise, ID, FROM: Aug. 22, 1993; Aug. 22, 1995 (personal file); TO: Sep. 21, 1995
  - Rockefeller, David, FROM: Aug. 9, 1993: TO: Aug. 27, 1993
  - Rocker, David A. Rocker Partners,L.P. FROM: Dec. 1, 1994; Sep. 18, 1995; Apr. 25, 1996; May 16, 1996; May 22, 1996; Mar. 5, 1998; Mar. 27, 1998; Jan. 27, 2000; Mar. 14, 2000; TO: Oct. 11, 1995; May 9, 1996; Jun. 26, 1996; Mar. 18, 1998; Apr. 17, 1998; Feb. 15, 2000; Apr. 24, 2000
  - Rodominick, Jarrod Boy Scouts of America, TO: Mar. 24, 1998
  - Roemer, Tim US House of Representatives, FROM: Jan. 20, 2000; TO: May 19, 2000
  - Rogers, Harold US House of Representatives, TO: Dec. 29, 1995; Jul. 29, 1999
  - Rogers, James E. Cinergy Corporation, TO: Dec. 5, 1997
  - Rogers, John W. Ariel Capital Management, Inc. FROM: Mar. 15, 1999; TO: Apr. 22, 1999
  - Rogers, Thomasina V. US Administrative Conference, FROM: Jun. 5, 1995; TO: Jun. 14, 1995
  - Rogers, William L. Colony Capital, Inc. FROM: Jul. 25, 1997; TO: Jul. 28, 1997
  - Rognovitz, Ruth US SEC - Office of International Affairs, TO: Dec. 18, 1995
  - Rogstad, Barry K. American Business Conference, FROM: Nov. 22, 1995; Feb. 20, 1997; Jun. 3, 1997; Sep. 29, 1998 (filed under Frazier, Fran, Oct. 2, 1998); Jul. 14, 2000; TO: Dec. 7, 1995; Mar. 4, 1997; Jun. 18, 1997; Sep. 18, 2000
  - Rolland, Ian M. Lincoln National Life Insurance Company, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Rollins, Loretta Municipal Securities Rulemaking Board, TO: Feb. 17, 1995
  - Rollwagen, John A. St. Paul Venture Capital, FROM: Apr. 11, 1997
  - Romano, Richard C. Romano Brothers & Co. TO: Feb. 17, 1995
  - Roper, Barbara L.N. Consumer Federation of America, FROM: Apr. 10, 1997; Aug. 1, 2000; TO: Apr. 20, 1995; Mar. 6, 1996; May 2, 1996; Apr. 30, 1997; Sep. 7, 2000
  - Roper, Joseph C. TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Rosen, Howard Competitiveness Policy Council, FROM: Mar. 26, 1996; TO: Apr. 15, 1996
  - Rosenberg, Henry A. Crown Central Petroleum Corp. TO: Apr. 6, 1995
  - Rosenberg, Nathan Owen Rosenberg Group, FROM: Jul. 30, 1993; TO: Aug. 12, 1993
  - Rosenberg, Wolfgang H. FROM: Jun. 29, 1996; TO: Jul. 17, 1996
  - Rosenblatt, Peter R. Heller, Rosen & Scheman; Heller & Rosenblatt, FROM: Dec. 10, 1996; Sep. 26, 2000; TO: Sep. 18, 1995
  - Rosenfield, Maurice, FROM: Sep. 19, 1994; Feb. 28, 1996; TO: Oct. 5, 1994; Mar. 13, 1996
  - Rosenman, Robert Cravath, Swaine & Moore, TO: Feb. 27, 1998
  - Rosenwald, E. John, Jr. Bear, Stearns & Co., Inc. FROM: Apr. 6, 1998; Sep. 9, 1999; TO: Apr. 6, 1998; Sep. 22, 1999
  - Rossi, Charles V. Securities Transfer Association, Inc. FROM: Sep. 5, 1997; TO: Sep. 18, 1997
  - Roth, Michael J.C. USAA Investment Management Co. TO: Mar. 16, 1999
  - Roth, William V., Jr. US Senate, TO: Feb. 17, 1995; Nov. 15, 1995; Jan. 3, 1996; Nov. 20, 1997
  - Rothenberg, James F. Capital Research and Management Company, FROM: Sep. 13, 1999; TO: Sep. 30, 1999
  - Rowe, John W. New England Electric System, TO: Dec. 5, 1997
  - Roy, P. Norman Financial Executives Institute, FROM: Mar. 22, 1995; TO: Apr. 18, 1995; Feb. 7, 1996; May 20, 1996 (Cook, Michael J.)
  - Roye, Paul F. US SEC - Division of Investment Management, FROM: Apr. 12, 1999 (Silver, David); TO: Feb. 26, 1999
  - Roybal-Allard, Lucille US House of Representatives, FROM: Dec. 10, 1997; TO: Jan. 20, 1998
  - Rubin, Robert E. US Department of Treasury; US Council on Foreign Relations, TO: [Mar. 14], 1995; May 16, 1995; Jun. 16. 1995; [Jun. 19, 1995]; Jun. 20, 1995; Sep. 4, 1996; Nov. 5, 1996; Jan. 9, 1997; Feb. 20, 1997; Jul. 16, 1998; Oct. 16, 1998; Sep. 28, 1999
  - Rubinstein, Peter J. Central Synagogue, TO: Aug. 2, 2000
  - Rudell, Joel M. Kavanagh Peters Powell & Osnato, TO: Aug. 5, 1993
  - Ruder, David S. Northwestern University - School of Law, FROM: Oct. 24, 1996 (RE: Anna Eshoo); Jul. 26, 2000; TO: Oct. 5, 1995; Oct. 23 1995; Nov. 5, 1996; May 27, 1997(Balamaci, N.); Jul. 28, 2000; Aug. 17, 2000
  - Ruder, William William Ruder, Inc. FROM: Feb. 22, 1995; Jan. 18, 1996; Oct. 15, 1997; Mar. 12, 1998; TO: Mar. 7, 1995; Jan. 30, 1996; Oct. 30, 1997; Mar. 17, 1998
  - Ruggieri, Bernard J. FROM: Aug. 12, 1993: TO: Aug. 27, 1993
  - Ruhlin, Peggy M. International Association for Financial Planning, FROM: Jun. 24, 1997; TO: Jul. 16, 1997
  - Rupp, George Columbia University, TO: Dec. 23, 1998
  - Ruru, Bacelius Capital Market Supervisory Agency, Indonesia, TO: Mar. 22, 1995; May 5, 1995
  - Rusenko, Harriet J. TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Rush, Bobby L. US House of Representatives, FROM: Nov. 20, 1997; TO: Jan. 20, 1998
  - Russo, Thomas A. Lehman Brothers, FROM: Jan. 20, 1997; TO: Feb. 4, 1997
  - Rustin, Richard E. FROM: Apr. 14, 1998
  - Ruth, Heather L. Public Securities Association, FROM: Feb. 24, 1995; TO: Mar. 16, 1995; Apr. 26, 1995
  - Ryan, Thomas P. Dean Witter Reynolds, Inc. TO: Sep. 13, 1995
  - Ryen, Christopher Boy Scouts of America, TO: Mar. 24, 1998
  - Sack, Joe Bond Market Association, TO: Apr. 14, 1998; May 22, 2000
  - Sadano, Salvatore American Stock Exchange, TO: Oct. 1, 1999; Nov. 10, 1999
  - Sadlin, Max US House of Representatives, FROM: Jan. 20, 2000; TO: May 19, 2000
  - Safire, William New York Times, TO: Sep. 26, 1996; Mar. 4, 1997; Jul. 23, 1997; Apr. 15, 1998; May 6, 1998
  - Saint-Geours, Jean Commission des Operations de Bourse, France, TO: Jan. 17, 1995
  - Salig, Ronald J. Boy Scouts of America, FROM: Dec. 8, 1997 (filed under Jason Desrosiers, Jan.14, 1998); Jan. 19, 1998; (Filed under Mar. 24, 1998)
  - Saloom, Joseph A. US Embassy, Germany, TO: Mar. 2, 1998
  - Saltzman, Paul Bond Market Association, FROM: Oct. 20, 1997; TO: Nov. 13, 1997
  - Samansky, Art Securities Industry Association, TO: Feb. 17, 1995
  - Sanders, Bernard US House of Representatives, FROM: Oct. 10, 1996; TO: Dec. 10, 1996
  - Sanderson, Janet US Embassy, Cairo, TO: Feb. 27, 1996
  - Sandner, John F. Chicago Mercantile Exchange, FROM: Jun. 21, 1995; Feb. 18, 1997; TO: Jul. 17, 1995; Mar. 4, 1997
  - Sands, Jerome Robinson Humphrey Co., LLC. TO: Mar. 27, 1995; Jun. 7, 1995
  - Sanford, Henry J. US Naval Academy, TO: Jan. 2, 1998
  - Sanford, Terry Duke University - Terry Sanford Institute of Public Policy, FROM: Jan. 28, 1997 (RE: Chestnutt, William J.); TO: Feb. 21, 1997
  - Sangvian Indaravijaya Stock Exchange, Thailand, TO: May 5, 1995
  - Santorum, Richard US Senate, FROM: Oct. 29, 1996; May 2, 2000; TO: Dec. 5, 1996; Jun. 27, 2000
  - Santos, Rich Registered Representative Magazine, TO: Jun. 21, 1999; Nov. 9, 2000
  - Saperstain, Michael Bear, Stearns & Co., Inc. TO: Oct. 18, 1993
  - Sarbanes, Paul S. US Senate, FROM: Sep. 28, 1995; Jan. 28, 2000; TO: Aug. 10, 1995; Oct. 31, 1995; Jan. 19, 1996; May 16, 1997; Sep. 25, 1997; Oct. 10, 1997; Sep. 30, 1998; Dec. 23, 1998; Mar. 14, 2000
  - Sargent, George K. TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Sargent, Holly Taylor Harvard University - John F. Kennedy School of Government, FROM: Aug. 15, 1995; TO: Sep. 12, 1995
  - Sarrazin, Jurgen Dresdner Bank AG, Germany, FROM: Apr. 10, 1995; TO: May 12, 1995
  - Santangelo, William Public Securities Association, FROM: Oct. 2, 1996; TO: Sep. 2, 1997
  - Sato, Ginko Securities and Exchange Surveillance Commission, Japan, TO: Aug. 17, 1998
  - Sauer, Kristen Dow Jones & Co. TO: Mar. 28, 1995
  - Saul, Ralph S. FROM: Sep. 27, 1999; TO: Nov. 1, 1999
  - Savage, Frank Alliance Capital Management, Inc. TO: Jan. 29, 2001
  - Saxon, Donald Department of Banking and Finance, FL - Office of Comptroller, TO: Feb. 17, 1995; TO: Apr. 21, 1995
  - Sayer, Ira, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Sayer, Paul US House of Representatives - Office of Richard Baker, TO:(Kathryn Fulton) Mar. 3, 1995
  - Sayers, Dorothy Sacred Heart University, FROM: Feb. 10, 1995; TO: Mar. 17, 1995
  - Scalia, Antonin US Supreme Court, TO: Oct. 5, 1998
  - Scardino, Jennifer US SEC - Chief of Staff, FROM: Apr. 6, 1997 (RE: Callaway, Howard); Dec. 23, 1997 (clippings)
  - Scardino, Marjorie Economist Group; Pearsons, UK, TO: Nov. 30, 1995; Dec. 13, 1996; Dec. 23, 1998; Apr. 27, 2000; Jan. 29, 2001
  - Schadt, James P. Reader's Digest Association, FROM: Oct. 27, 1993; Jan. 5, 1995; TO: Jan. 19, 1995; Dec. 18, 1995; Dec. 19, 1996
  - Schaefer, Jeffrey M. Securities Industry Association, FROM: Aug. 16, 1993; Dec. 13, 1995; TO: Aug. 24, 1993; Jan. 2, 1996
  - Schaler, Ralph G. Merrill Lynch & Co., Inc. FROM: Sep. 2, 1993: TO: Sep. 15, 1993
  - Schapiro, Mary L. Commodity Futures Trading Commission; National Association of Securities Dealers Regulation, Inc. FROM: Dec. 22, 1994; Jan. 26, 1995; Jun. 15, 1995; TO: Jan. 10, 1995; [Feb. 13, 1995]; Jun. 28, 1995; Feb. 8, 1996; Apr. 10, 1997; Apr. 30, 1997; Jun. 9, 1997; Oct. 3, 1997 (filed under Markey, Oct. 3, 1997)
  - Scharver, Chris Boston Stock Exchange Specialist Association, FROM: Jun. 10, 1998; TO: Jun. 30, 1998
  - Schechter, William William Schechter Inc. FROM: Mar. 3, 1998; TO: Apr. 16, 1998
  - Schieren, George A. Merrill Lynch, Pierce, Fenner & Smith, Inc. FROM: Jan. 31, 1997; TO: May 1, 1995; Feb. 26, 1997
  - Schiffman US SEC, TO: May 3, 1995
  - Schiro, James J. PriceWaterhouseCoopers, FROM: Jun. 12, 1998; Aug. 17, 2000; TO: Jul. 10, 1998; Aug. 29, 2000; Nov. 27, 2000; Jan. 29, 2001
  - Schlafly, Phyllis Eagle Forum, FROM: May 9, 2000; TO: Jun. 20, 2000
  - Schlein, Michael E. US SEC - Counsel, TO: Feb. 17 1995
  - Schlimmer, Karl Boy Scouts of America, TO: Mar. 24, 1998
  - Schlosser, Alfred M. FROM: Mar. 15, 1999; TO: Mar. 18, 1999
  - Schmelzer, Henry L.P. New England Securities, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Schmitt, Christopher H. Business Week, FROM: Oct. 18, 2000; TO: Nov. 27, 2000
  - Schneider, Steven L. Disclosure, Inc. FROM: Sep. 7, 1995 (filed under Morella, Oct. 20, 1995)
  - Schoenberger, Robert G. Unitil Service Corporation, TO: Dec. 5, 1997
  - Scholl, Herb, TO: Jan. 10, 2001
  - Schori, Pierre Ministry for Foreign Affairs, Sweden; European Parliament; FROM: Oct. 29, 1993; Aug. 23, 1996; Nov. 1, 1999; TO: Sep. 5, 1996; Nov. 22, 1999
  - Schosberg, Paul A. America's Community Bankers, FROM: Jul. 28, 1993; Mar. 11, 1998; TO: Aug. 4, 1993; Mar. 17, 1998
  - Schrader, William L. PSINet, Inc. TO: Apr. 17, 1998
  - Schroeder, Harald J. Merck KGaA, Germany, TO: Apr. 25, 1997
  - Schroeder, John W. Advanced Micro Devices, Inc. FROM: Feb. 15, 1995; TO: Feb. 23, 1995
  - Schroeder, Patricia Association of American Publishers, TO: Mar. 31, 1999; Mar. 28, 2000
  - Schubert, Daniel MetroHealth Medical Center, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Schubert, Jeffrey Principal Financial Securities, Inc. TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Schuetze, Walter P. FROM: Mar. 29, 1996; TO: Apr. 11, 1996
  - Schulte, David M. Chilmark Partners, FROM: Oct. 28, 1997 (RE: Alison Landsberg; TO: Nov. 26, 1997
  - Schulze, Erwin E. Chicago Stock Exchange, FROM: Apr. 18, 1996; TO: Feb. 17 1995; Jul. 7, 1995; May 21, 1996
  - Schumer, Charles E. US House of Representatives; US Senate, FROM: May 14, 1997; Jul. 7, 1997; Dec. 18, 1997; Feb. 24, 1998; Apr. 20, 1999 (2); May 25, 2000; Jul. 17, 2000 (Susan Wyderko, RE: Restivo, Peter; Edwards, Denver); TO: Aug. 1, 1997; Feb. 25, 1998; Mar. 18, 1998; Apr. 23, 1999; Oct. 14, 1999; Dec. 22, 19
  - Schutt, Steve DLS Group, Inc. TO: Feb. 17 1995
  - Schwab, Charles R. Charles Schwab & Co, Inc, TO: Mar. 2, 1995; Mar. 27, 1995; Apr. 20, 1995; Jun. 7, 1995; Apr. 10, 1996; Mar. 16, 1999
  - Schwab, Richard L. ZD Comdex & Forums, TO: Jan. 25, 1999
  - Schwartz, Howard J. Lynch, Jones & Ryan, Inc. FROM: Feb. 5, 1998; TO: May 17, 1995; Mar. 4, 1998
  - Schwartz, Mark Council Member, OK City; National League of Cities, FROM: Mar. 18, 1997; May 6, 1998; TO: Mar. 26, 1997; Jun. 16, 1998
  - Schwartz, Robert, S. Prudential Securities, Inc. FROM: Nov. 27, 1995; TO: Dec. 18, 1995
  - Scottt, Charles Red, FROM: Jan. 19, 1996 (RE: Klein, Mel)
  - Schwarz-Schutte, Patrick Schwarz Pharma AG, Germany, TO: Apr. 25, 1997
  - Scott, Richard L. Columbia/HCA Healthcare Corporation, TO: May 3, 1995
  - Scott, Kenneth E. Stanford Law School, TO: Mar. 16, 1999
  - Searll, Aaron Seardel Investment Corporation, Republic of South Africa, FROM: Mar. 8, 1995; TO: Mar. 7, 1995
  - Segal, Martin E. FROM: Jun. 4, 1996; Apr. 8, 1998; Sep. 10, 1998; TO: Jun. 10, 1996; Apr. 15, 1998; Nov. 4, 1998
  - Segreti, Joseph US SEC - Web Development, TO: Sep. 29, 1995
  - Seidel, Heather US SEC - Division of Market Regulation, TO: Nov. 16, 1998
  - Seiden, Steven Seiden Krieger Associates, Inc. FROM: Apr. 13, 1998; TO: Apr. 21, 1998
  - Seidenberg, Ivan Bell Atlantic, TO: Dec. 20, 1999
  - Seidman, Ellen White House, FROM: Feb. 24, 1994
  - Seijas, Robert W. Specialists Association at the New York Stock Exchange, FROM: Jun. 10, 1998; TO: Jun. 30, 1998
  - Selbst, Stanton C. Selbst Group, Inc. FROM: Oct. 21, 1998; TO: Nov. 17, 1998
  - Seldes, Aileen Patterson, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Seligman, Joel University of Michigan, MI - School of Law; University of Arizona, AZ - Law School, FROM: Jan. 14, 1997; TO: Jan. 25, 1995; Oct. 23 1995; Feb. 4, 1997; May 27, 1997(Balamaci, N.); Aug. 29, 1997
  - Selvagn, Matthew Boy Scouts of America, TO: Mar. 24, 1998
  - Senatore, Charles V. US SEC - Southeast Regional Office; Merrill Lynch, TO: Dec. 30, 1996; Sep. 28, 1999
  - Sener, John E. TO: Sep. 26, 1996 (RE: Platt, Martha H.)
  - Senger, Henry C. SmithBarney, FROM: Jan. 22, 1998; TO: Feb. [10], 1998
  - Seri, Chintanaseri Stock Exchange, Thailand, TO: May 5, 1995
  - Sessions, Pete US House of Representatives, FROM: Mar. 5, 1997; [n.d.] (fragment); TO: Apr. 4, 1997
  - Settel, Jim Prudential Securities, Inc. TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Sewll, Stephen F. FROM: Feb. 13, 1996; TO: Feb. 27, 1996
  - Sexton, John New York University - School of Law, TO: Apr. 26, 1995
  - Shackman Jacoby, Daniel B. Shackman & Co. TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Shad, John, TO: Aug. 6, 1993
  - Shafer, Jeffrey US Department of Treasury, TO: Feb. 7, 1996
  - Shafroth, Frank National League of Cities, TO: Jan. 9, 1997
  - Shagrin, Donald M. FROM: Jul. 25, 1993; TO: Sep. 13, 1993
  - Shands, Susan Office of the Secretary of State, MS, TO: Apr. 21, 1995
  - Shanklin, Robert F. US SEC - Desktop Publishing, TO: Oct. 6, 1997
  - Shapiro, Robert F. Klingstein Fields & Co, LLC, FROM: Jul. 27, 2000; TO: Aug. 15, 2000
  - Sharp, Daniel A. American Assembly, FROM: Jan. 3, 1997; TO: Jan. 21, 1997
  - Shattuck, Mayo A. BT Alex Brown Inc. TO: Apr. 8, 1998
  - Shaver, Troy C. John Hancock Broker Distribution Services, Inc. TO: Mar 2, 1995; Apr. 20, 1995
  - Shaw, Eugene, FROM: [Dec. 27, 1995]; TO: Jul. 31, 1996
  - Shaw, Meddi, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Shea, Daniel F. US SEC - Central Regional Office, TO: Dec. 30, 1996
  - Shedlarz, David L. Pfizer Inc. TO: Jun. 13, 2000
  - Sheinkman, Jack AFL-CIO, FROM: Aug. 19, 1997; TO: Sep. 11, 1997
  - Shelby, Richard C. US Senate, FROM: Jun. 5, 1996; Jan. 17, 1997; Jul. 2, 1997; TO: Jun. 24, 1996; Feb. 10, 1997; Jul. 24, 1997; Aug. 21, 2000
  - Shell, Callie White House, FROM: [Apr.] 1996; TO: Apr. 18, 1996
  - Shelton, George Howe Barnes Investments, Inc. TO: Sep. 13, 1995
  - Shen, Andrew Electronic Privacy Information Center, FROM: May 9, 2000; TO: Jun. 20, 2000
  - Sheng, Andrew L. T. Securities and Futures Commission, Hong Kong, FROM: Nov. 24, 1998; TO: Nov. 19, 1998; Mar. 3, 1999; Jan. 29, 2001
  - Shepard, Steven Business Week, FROM: Sep. 28, 2000; TO: Jan. 29, 2001
  - Shepheard-Walwyn, Tim Securities and Investments Board, UK, FROM: Mar. 3, 1995; TO: (Whittaker) Mar. 6, 1995
  - Sherlund, Richard Goldman Sachs & Co. TO: Jun. 13, 2000
  - Sherman, Brad US House of Representatives, FROM: Dec. 10, 1997; TO: Jan. 20, 1998
  - Sherman, Donald A. US SEC - Office of Administrative and Personnel Support, FROM: Dec. 23, 1999 (Fenster, Herbert)
  - Sherman, Derek, FROM: Jan. 23, 1996; TO: Feb. 20, 1996
  - Sherman, John, Jr. Scott & Stringfellow, Inc. FROM: Apr. 24, 1998; TO: May 28, 1998
  - Sherman, Lawrence F. Mony Securities Corp. TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Sherrill, David, TO: Apr. 26, 1995
  - Sherrill, H. Virgil Prudential Securities, Inc. FROM: Jul. 27, 2000; TO: Aug. 15, 2000
  - Shilling, A. Gary A. Gary Shilling & Co., Inc. FROM: Aug. 29, 1997; TO: Nov. 28, 1995; Dec. 19, 1996; Sep. 17, 1997; Dec. 13, 1999
  - Shin, Young Moo Shin & Kim, Seoul, Korea, FROM: Mar. 10, 1995; TO: (Michael Mann) Apr. 17, 1997
  - Shipley, Walter Chase Manhattan Corp. TO: Dec. 28, 1998
  - Shipp, Chris Prudential Insurance Company of America, TO: Feb. 17 1995
  - Shreve, Richard S. Dartmouth College, TO: Apr. 26, 1995
  - Shrontz, Frank A. Boeing, TO: May 1, 1995
  - Sibears, Daniel M. National Association of Securities Dealers, TO: Feb. 17 1995
  - Siebert, Muriel (Mickie) Muriel Siebert & Co., Inc. FROM: Aug. 12, 1998; TO: Aug. 19, 1998
  - Siegel, Paul F. Prudential Securities, Inc. FROM: Apr. 1, 1998; Dec. 3, 1998; TO: Apr. 30, 1998; Dec. 16, 1998
  - Silby, Barbara, FROM: Jul. 27, 1993; TO: Aug. 4, 1993
  - Silver, Jonathan M. Commonwealth Holdings, Inc. FROM: Mar. 20, 1998; TO: Mar. 25, 1998
  - Silverman, Jeffrey S. Ply Gem Industries, Inc. TO: Dec. 13, 1995
  - Silva, Francisco Augusto da Costa e Comissao de Valores Mobiliarios, Brazil, TO: Jul. 3, 1996; Nov. 19, 1998; Mar. 3, 1999; Jun. 22, 1999; [Nov.]. 1999
  - Silver, Bob PaineWebber, TO: Apr. 26, 1995
  - Silver, David ICI Mutual Insurance Company, FROM: Apr. 1, 1997; Apr. 9, 1998; Apr. 1, 1999; TO: Apr. 21, 1997; Apr. 30, 1998; Apr. 12, 1999
  - Silver, Gordon H. Putnam Investments, FROM: Oct. 23, 1996; TO: Nov. 14, 1996
  - Silverstone, Leslie J. FROM: [Apr. 1998]; TO: Apr. 26, 1995; Apr. 15, 1998
  - Simon, Moshe US SEC - Office of the General Counsel, TO: Jul. 15, 1996
  - Simon, Paul US Senate, FROM: Nov. 9, 1995; Sep. 20, 1996; TO: Nov. 27, 1995; Oct. 31, 1996
  - Silvester, Paul J. Treasurer, CT, FROM: Dec. 12, 1997; TO: Jan. 8, 1998
  - Simmons, Hardwick Prudential Securities, Inc. FROM: Jun. 13 1996; Sep. 11, 1998; Mar. 31, 1999; Jun. 7, 1999; NOv. 3, 1999; Jan. 3, 2000; TO: Feb. 17, 1995; Mar 2, 1995; Mar. 27, 1995; Apr. 20, 1995; Jun. 7, 1995; Jul. 11, 1996; Sep. 13, 1996; Jan. 30. 1997; Oct. 17, 1997; Oct. 23, 1997; Apr. 8, 19
  - Simmons, Michelle New York Stock Exchange, TO: Feb. 17 1995
  - Simmons, William R. Dean Witter Reynolds, Inc. TO: Feb. 17 1995
  - Simons, W. Lucas J.C. Bradford & Co. TO: Aug. 23, 1995
  - Singerman, Martin New York Post, TO: May 8, 1998
  - Siphron, David C. Siphron Capital Management, FROM: Jun. 6, 1997; TO: Aug. 1, 1997
  - Siravo, George, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Smith, James N. Council of Infrastructure Financing Authorities, TO: Jan. 9, 1997
  - Smith, John M. Guardian Investor Services Corporation, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Sirri, Erik R. US SEC - Office of Economic Analysis, TO: Feb. 26, 1999; Jul. 19, 1999
  - Sisso, Shmuel Consulate General of Israel in New York, FROM: Aug. 18, 1998 (filed under Netanyahu, Oct. 5, 1998)
  - Sizemore, Douglas M. FROM: Nov. 27, 1995; TO: Dec. 18, 1995
  - Skates, Ronald L. Data General Corporation, TO: Feb. 19, 1999
  - Skogstad Aamo, Bjorn Kredittilsynet, Norway, TO: Apr. 10, 1997
  - Skolnik, Bradley W. North American Securities Administrators Association, Inc - Securities Commission, IN, TO: Apr. 21, 1995; Mar. 16, 1999
  - Slomka, Lars Berliner Borsenkreis e. V., Germany, FROM: Aug. 6, 1995; TO: Aug. 22 1995
  - Slonaker, Norman D. Brown & Wood, TO: Feb. 27, 1998
  - Sloves, Martin Lowe & Partners, FROM: Oct. 16, 1995; TO: Oct. 24, 1995